Guide to the American Business Consultants, Inc. Counterattack: Research Files TAM 148
Tamiment Library / Wagner Archives
- Series 12: Communist Party, USA Front Organizations.
  - *China Welfare Fund, 1948-1955 (Box 17, Folder 12-87)
  - National Council for American Education, 1948 (Box 17, Folder 12-88)
  - Council on Foreign Relations, 1949, 1963 (Box 17, Folder 12-89)
  - Association of Interns and Medical Students, 1947-1949 (Box 17, Folder 12-90)
  - *National Council of the Arts, Sciences and Professions, 1948-1953 (Box 17, Folder 12-91)
  - Committee for Free Political Inquiry, 1949 (Box 17, Folder 12-92)
  - Committee for the Negro in the Arts, 1949 (Box 18, Folder 12-93)
  - World Federation of Democratic Youth, 1947-1949 (Box 18, Folder 12-94)
  - *World Youth Festival (Budapest, 1949) (Box 18, Folder 12-94a)
  - *Bill of Rights Conference, NYC, 1949 (Box 18, Folder 12-95)
  - *Voice of Freedom Committee, 1949 (Box 18, Folder 12-96)
  - MidWest Farmer-Labor Committee, 1949 (Box 18, Folder 12-97)
  - People's Artists Inc. and People's Songs, 1947-1949 (Box 18, Folder 12-98)
  - One World Award Committee, 1948-1949 (Box 18, Folder 12-99)
  - Contemporary Writers, 1948 (Box 18, Folder 12-100)
  - *The Churchman, 1948-1949 (Box 18, Folder 12-101)
  - The Asia Institute, undated (Box 18, Folder 12-102)
  - American Slav Congress, 1949 (Box 18, Folder 12-103)
  - National Labor Conference for Peace, 1949 (Box 18, Folder 12-104)
  - *Methodist Federation for Social Action, 1947-1951 (Box 18, Folder 12-105)
  - *Dramatic Workshop & Technical Institute, 1949 (Box 18, Folder 12-106)
  - National Non-Partisan Committee to Defend the Rights of the 12 Communist Leaders, 1949 (Box 18, Folder 12-107)
  - United Productions of America, 1945-1950 (Folder 12-108)
  - Tempo Films, 1950 (Folder 12-109)
  - *Supporters of Communist Front Organizations or Campaigns, 1944-1948 (Folder 12-110)
  - *Peace Organizations, 1949-1952 (Folder 12-111v.1)
  - Peace Organizations, 1950-1952 (Folder 12-111v.2)
  - *Emergency Civil Liberties Committee, 1953-1955 (Folder 12-112)
  - Teachers and Professors, 1945-1953 (Folder 12-113)
  - Communism in the Motion Picture Industry (a manual), 1960 (Folder 12-114)
  - American Women Visit the Kremlin, 1957-1958 (Folder 12-115)
- Series 13: Communist Party - Influenced trade unions.
  - (pg# no pgs ) Union Index, undated (Box 19, Folder 13-0)
  - (pg# 13-0/ ) 1-36, Unions General1949- (Box 19)
  - (pg# 1-45 ) World Federation of Trade Unions, 1943-1952 (Box 19, Folder 13-1)
  - World Federation of Trade Unions, 1946-1949 (Box 19, Folder 13-1 sup)
  - (pg# 1-17 ) 2nd World Trade Union Congress, 1949 (Box 19, Folder 13-1-A)
  - (pg# 1-3 ) Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America, 1945-1953 (Box 19, Folder 13-2)
  - Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America, 1948-1949 (Box 19, Folder 13-2 sup)
  - (pg# 1-52 ) *American Communication Association, Volume I, 1937-1948 (Box 19, Folder 13-3)
  - (pg# 53-54 ) *American Communication Association, Volume II, 1946-1965 (Box 19, Folder 13-3)
  - *American Communications Association, 1941-1950 (Box 19, Folder 13-3 sup)
  - (pg# no pgs. ) *American Radio Association, 1947-1949 (Box 19, Folder 13-3A-1)
  - (pg# no pgs. ) *American Radio Association, 1947-1948 (Box 19, Folder 13-3A-2)
  - (pg# no pgs ) *American Radio Association, 1948 (Box 19, Folder 13-3A-3)
  - (pg# 1-14 ) American Newspaper Guild, 1937-1947 (Box 19, Folder 13-4)
  - American Newspaper Guild, 1948-1949 (Box 19, Folder 13-4 sup)
  - (pg# 1 ) Barber and Beauty Culturists of America, 1945 (Box 19, Folder 13-5)
  - American Beauty Culturists of America, 1948-1949 (Box 19, Folder 13-5 sup)
  - (pg# 1-2 ) International Federation of Architects, Engineers, Chemists, and Technicians, 1942-1945 (Box 19, Folder 13-6)
  - (pg# 1 ) Federation of Glass, Ceramic and Silica-Sand Workers of America, .undated (Box 19, Folder 13-7)
  - (pg# 1-4 ) Food, Tobacco, Agricultural and Allied Workers Union of America, 1945-1947 (Box 19, Folder 13-8)
  - Food, Tobacco, Agricultural and Allied Workers Union of America, 1947-1949 (Box 19, Folder 13-8 sup)
  - (pg# 1-16 ) Hotel and Restaurant Employees International Alliance and Bartenders International League of America, 1946-1951 (Box 19, Folder 13-9)
  - (pg# 1-10 ) International Union of Marine and Shipbuilding Workers of America, CIO, 1948-1949 (Box 19, Folder 13-10)
  - (pg# 1 ) Inland Boatman Union of the Pacific, undated (Box 19, Folder 13-11)
  - (pg# 1-5 ) International Fur and Leather Workers Union, 1938-1947 (Box 19, Folder 13-12)
  - International Fur and Leather Workers Union, 1942-1953 (Box 19, Folder 13-12 sup)
  - (pg# 1-8 ) International Longshoreman's and Warehouseman's Union, 1947-1948 (Box 19, Folder 13-13)
  - International Longshoreman's and Warehouseman's Union, 1947-1952 (Box 19, Folder 13-13 sup)
  - (pg# 1-12 ) International Union of Mine, Mill and Smelter Workers, 1946-1952 (Box 19, Folder 13-14)
  - No Title, undated (Box 20, Folder No File#)
  - International Union of Mine, Mill and Smelter Workers, 1947-1950 (Box 20, Folder 13-14 sup)
  - (pg# 1 ) International Woodworkers of America, 1945 (Box 20, Folder 13-15)
  - International Woodworkers of America, 1941-1949 (Box 20, Folder 13-15 sup)
  - (pg# 1-3 ) National Union of Marine Cooks' and Stewards' Association, 1945-1947 (Box 20, Folder 13-16)
  - National Union of Marine Cooks and Stewards, 1948-1950 (Box 20, Folder 13-16 sup)
  - (pg# 1-5 ) Marine Engineers Beneficial Association (National), 1946-1949 (Box 20, Folder 13-17)
  - Marine Engineers Beneficial Association, 1948-1949 (Box 20, Folder 13-17 sup)
  - (pg# 1-50 ) National Maritime Union, 1945-1950 (Box 20, Folder 13-18)
  - National Maritime Union, 1947-1949 (Box 20, Folder 13-18 sup-1)
  - National Maritime Union, 1946-1949 (Box 20, Folder 13-18 sup-2)
  - (pg# 1 ) Optical and Instrument Workers Organizing Committee, undated (Box 20, Folder 13-20)
  - (pg# 1 ) Paper Workers Organizing Committee, 1945 (Box 20, Folder 13-21)
  - (pg# 1-2 ) Plaything, Jewelry and Novelty Workers International Union, 1947 (Box 20, Folder 13-22)
  - (pg# 1 ) Plumbers and Steamfitters of the United States and Canada, 1946 (Box 20, Folder 13-23)
  - (pg# 1-8 ) Sugar Refinery Workers, 1946 (Box 20, Folder 13-24)
  - (pg# 1-49 ) *Transport Workers Union, 1933-1951 (Box 20, Folder 13-25)
  - *Transport Workers Union, 1947-1949 (Box 20, Folder 13-25 sup)
  - (pg# 1-46 ) United Automobile, Aircraft, and Agricultural Implement, 1945-1948 (Box 20, Folder 13-26)
  - Workers of America, CIO, undated (Box 20)
  - United Automobile, Aircraft, and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, CIO, 1940-1951 (Box 20, Folder 13-26 sup)
  - undated (Box 20)
  - (pg# 1-60 ) *United Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers of America, 1942-1952 (Box 20, Folder 13-27)
  - (pg# 60-69 ) *United Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers of America, 1947-1949 (Box 20, Folder 13-27)
  - *United Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers of America, 1949-1950 (Box 20, Folder 13-27 sup-1)
  - *United Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers of America, 1944-1955 (Box 20, Folder 13-27 sup-2)
  - *United Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers of America, 1950 (Box 20, Folder 13-27 sup-3)
  - *United Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers of America, 1949-1950 (Box 20, Folder 13-27 sup-4)
  - *United Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers of America- Publications, 1942-1951 (Box 20, Folder 13-27 sup-5)
  - Removed Material, undated (Box 20, Folder No File#)
  - United Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers of America, 1952 (Box 21, Folder 13-27 sup-6)
  - United Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers of America, 1947-1949 (Box 21, Folder 13-27 sup-7)
  - (pg# 1-5 ) United Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers of America, Local 430, 1945-1948 (Box 21, Folder 13-27A)
  - (pg# 1-33 ) United Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers of America, Local 475, 1942-1950 (Box 21, Folder 13-27 B)
  - (pg# 1-16 ) United Farm Equipment and Metal Workers of America, 1945-1949 (Box 21, Folder 13-28)
  - United Farm Equipment and Metal Workers of America, 1948-1952 (Box 21, Folder 13-28 sup)
  - (pg# 1-13 ) United Furniture Workers of America, 1939-1946 (Box 21, Folder 13-29)
  - United Furniture Workers of America, 1949-1951 (Box 21, Folder 13-29 sup)
  - (pg# 1-5 ) United Gas, Coke, and Chemical Workers of America, 1947-1953 (Box 21, Folder 13-30)
  - United Gas, Coke, and Chemical Workers of America, 1947-1949 (Box 21, Folder 13-30 sup)
  - (pg# 1-54 ) *United Office and Professional Workers of America, 1941-1947 (Box 21, Folder 13-31)
  - (pg# 55-97 ) *United Office and Professional Workers of America, 1946-1950 (Box 21, Folder 13-31)
  - *United Office and Professional Workers of America, 1940-1950 (Box 21, Folder 13-31 sup-1)
  - *United Office and Professional Workers of America, 1942-1950 (Box 21, Folder 13-31 sup-2)
  - *United Office and Professional Workers of America, 1946-1950 (Box 21, Folder 13-31 sup-3)
  - (pg# 1-5 ) *United Packinghouse Workers of America, 1945-1954 (Box 21, Folder 13-32)
  - *United Packinghouse Workers of America, 1948-1951 (Box 21, Folder 13-32 sup)
  - (pg# 1-32 ) *United Public Workers of America, 1940-1949 (Box 21, Folder 13-33)
  - *United Public Workers of America, 1946-1952 (Box 21, Folder 13-33 sup)
  - (pg# 1-20 ) *United Public Workers of America, Local 555, 1940-1949 (Box 21, Folder 13-33 A)
  - (pg# 1-26 ) *Retail, Wholesale and Department Store Workers of America, 1938-1946 (Box 21, Folder 13-34)
  - (pg# 1-15, ) *Retail, Wholesale and Department Store Workers of America, 1946-1953 (Box 21, Folder 13-34 A)
  - (pg# 18-26, 28-41, 44-74) Removed Material, undated (Box 21, Folder No File#)
  - (pg# 1-2, 4-67, 69-81 ) *Retail, Wholesale and Department Store Workers of America, 1946-1948 (Box 21, Folder 13-34 B)
  - Packinghouse Workers Union, undated (Box 21, Folder No File#)
  - (pg# 1-21 ) Retail, Wholesale and Department Store Workers of America, Local 65, 1946-1948 (Box 22, Folder 13-34 C)
  - (pg# 1-57 ) Retail, Wholesale and Department Store Workers of America, 1946-1947 (Box 22, Folder 13-34 D)
  - (pg# 1-2 ) United Rubber Workers of America, 1947 (Box 22, Folder 13-35)
  - United Rubber Workers of America, 1948-1949 (Box 22, Folder 13-35 sup)
  - (pg# 1-11 ) United Shoe Workers of America, 1951 (Box 22, Folder 13-36)
  - United Shoe Workers of America, 1939-1955 (Box 22, Folder 13-36 sup)
  - (pg# 1-6 ) United Steelworkers of America, 1937-1948 (Box 22, Folder 13-37)
  - United Steelworkers of America, 1948-1949 (Box 22, Folder 13-37 sup)
  - (pg# 1 ) United Stone and Allied Product Workers of America, 1945 (Box 22, Folder 13-38)
  - (pg# 1-3 ) United Textile Workers Union of America, 1947-1948 (Box 22, Folder 13-39)
  - (pg# 1 ) United Transport Service Employees of America, undated (Box 22, Folder 13-40)
  - (pg# 1-3 ) United Utilities Union of America, 1945-1946 (Box 22, Folder 13-41)
  - (pg# 1-2 ) Utility Workers of America, 1946-1947 (Box 22, Folder 13-42)
  - Utility Workers of America, 1946-1949 (Box 22, Folder 13-42 sup)
  - (pg# 1-16 ) American Federation of Labor, 1946-1947 (Box 22, Folder 13-44)
  - American Federation of Labor, 1946-1949 (Box 22, Folder 13-44 sup)
  - (pg# 1-17 ) Greater New York Industrial Union Council, 1942-1948 (Box 22, Folder 13-45)
  - Greater New York Industrial Union Council-CIO, 1946-1949 (Box 22, Folder 13-45 sup)
  - (pg# 1-50 ) CIO National, 1946-1948 (Box 22, Folder 13-46)
  - CIO National, 1946-1949 (Box 22, Folder 13-46 sup-1)
  - CIO National, 1948-1950 (Box 22, Folder 13-46 sup-2)
  - CIO National, 1941-1952 (Box 22, Folder 13-46 sup-3)
  - (pg# no pgs ) CIO Convention #11, 1949 (Box 22, Folder 13-46 A)
  - (pg# 1 ) Marine Firemen, Oilers, Watertenders and Wipers of the Pacific Coast, 1946 (Box 22, Folder 13-47)
  - (pg# 1-5 ) United Financial Employees, 1946 (Box 22, Folder 13-48)
  - United Financial Employees, 1947-1948 (Box 22, Folder 13-48 sup)
  - (pg# 1-6 ) Railroad Unions, 1946-1947 (Box 22, Folder 13-49)
  - (pg# 1-12 ) United Mine Workers of America, 1947-1948 (Box 22, Folder 13-50)
  - United Mine Workers of America, 1948-1949 (Box 22, Folder 13-50 sup)
  - (pg# 1-2 ) International Ladies Garment Workers Union, 1946-1947 (Box 22, Folder 13-51)
  - International Ladies Garment Workers Union, 1946-1953 (Box 22, Folder 13-51 sup)
  - Removed Material, undated (Box 22, Folder No File#)
  - (pg# 1 ) Masters, Mates and Pilots, 1946 (Box 23, Folder 13-52)
  - Masters, Mates and Pilots, 1948-1949 (Box 23, Folder 13-52 sup)
  - (pg# 1-12a ) Screen Writers Guild, 1946-1951 (Box 23, Folder 13-53)
  - Screen Writers Guild, 1946-1949 (Box 23, Folder 13-53 sup)
  - (pg# 1-4 ) Newspaper Guild New York, 1947-1948 (Box 23, Folder 13-54)
  - (pg# 1-19 ) Taft-Hartley Bill, 1947-1948 (Box 23, Folder 13-55)
  - Taft-Hartley Bill, 1948-1949 (Box 23, Folder 13-55 sup)
  - (pg# 1-7 ) Marine Committee-CIO, 1947 (Box 23, Folder 13-56)
  - (pg# 1-2 ) American Federation of Musicians, 1947 (Box 23, Folder 13-57)
  - (pg# 1-8 ) National Labor Relations Board, 1947-1948 (Box 23, Folder 13-58)
  - National Labor Relations Board, 1947-1952 (Box 23, Folder 13-58 sup)
  - (pg# 1-5 ) Labor Legislature, 1947 (Box 23, Folder 13-59)
  - (pg# 1-4A ) Telephone Workers Organizing Committee, 1947 (Box 23, Folder 13-60)
  - Seaman's Union of the Pacific, 1937-1949 (Box 23, Folder 13-61 sup)
  - (pg# 1 ) Seafarer's International Union, 1947 (Box 23, Folder 13-62)
  - (pg# 1-5 ) Misc. Trade Unions, 1947 (Box 23, Folder 13-63)
  - Misc. Trade Unions, 1947-1950 (Box 23, Folder 13-63 sup-1)
  - Misc. Trade Unions, 1948-1950 (Box 23, Folder 13-63 sup-2)
  - Misc. Trade Unions, 1948-1950 (Box 23, Folder 13-63 sup-3)
  - (pg# 1-1A ) Actors Equity Association and Chorus Equity Association, 1949 (Box 23, Folder 13-64)
  - (pg# 1 ) Trade Union Service, 1948 (Box 23, Folder 13-65)
  - (pg# 1-16 ) Local 50, bakery and Confectionery Workers, 1948-1949 (Box 23, Folder 13-66)
  - (pg# 1 ) Retail Drug Employees Union, 1951 (Box 23, Folder 13-67)
  - Retail Drug Employees Union, 1948-1956 (Box 23, Folder 13-67 sup)
  - (pg# 1-4 ) Television Writers of America, 1953 (Box 23, Folder 13-68)
  - International Longshoreman's Association, AFL, 1948-1949 (Box 23, Folder 13-69 sup)
  - No Title, 1940-1949 (Box 23, Folder No File#)
  - Removed Materials, undated (Box 23, Folder No File#)
- Series 14.0: Individuals Miscellaneous
  - Communist Party - Individuals List, undated (Box 24, Folder 14-v.I)
  - (pg# 0-89 ) Individuals, miscellaneous, undated (Box 24, Folder 14-0)
  - (pg# 90-150 ) Individuals, miscellaneous, undated (Box 24, Folder 14-0)
  - (pg# 151-230 ) Individuals, miscellaneous, undated (Box 24, Folder 14-0)
  - (pg# 231-330 ) Individuals, miscellaneous, undated (Box 24, Folder 14-0)
  - (pg# 331-414 ) Individuals, miscellaneous, undated (Box 24, Folder 14-0)
  - (pg# 415-532 ) Individuals, miscellaneous, undated (Box 24, Folder 14-0)
  - (pg# 533-699 ) Individuals, miscellaneous, undated (Box 24, Folder 14-0)
  - (pg# 700-850 ) Individuals, miscellaneous, undated (Box 24, Folder 14-0)
  - (pg# 851-1028 ) Individuals, miscellaneous, undated (Box 24, Folder 14-0)
  - (pg# 1029-1224 ) Individuals, miscellaneous, undated (Box 24, Folder 14-0)
  - (pg# 1225-1389 ) Individuals, miscellaneous, undated (Box 24, Folder 14-0)
  - (pg# 1390-1474 ) Individuals, miscellaneous, undated (Box 24, Folder 14-0)
  - (pg# 1475-1549 ) Individuals, miscellaneous, undated (Box 24, Folder 14-0)
  - (pg# 1550-1625 ) Individuals, miscellaneous, undated (Box 24, Folder 14-0)
  - (pg# 1636-1684 ) Individuals, miscellaneous, undated (Box 25, Folder 14-0)
  - (pg# 1685-1759 ) Individuals, miscellaneous, undated (Box 25, Folder 14-0)
  - (pg# 1760-1839 ) Individuals, miscellaneous, undated (Box 25, Folder 14-0)
  - (pg# 1840-1926 ) Individuals, miscellaneous, undated (Box 25, Folder 14-0)
  - (pg# 1925A-1974 ) Individuals, miscellaneous, undated (Box 25, Folder 14-0)
  - (pg# 1975-2049 ) Individuals, miscellaneous, undated (Box 25, Folder 14-0)
  - (pg# 2050-2124 ) Individuals, miscellaneous, undated (Box 25, Folder 14-0)
  - (pg# 2125-2199 ) Individuals, miscellaneous, undated (Box 25, Folder 14-0)
  - (pg# 2200-2299 ) Individuals, miscellaneous, undated (Box 25, Folder 14-0)
  - (pg# 2300-2374 ) Individuals, miscellaneous, undated (Box 25, Folder 14-0)
  - (pg# 2375-2449 ) Individuals, miscellaneous, undated (Box 25, Folder 14-0)
  - (pg# 2450-2524 ) Individuals, miscellaneous, undated (Box 25, Folder 14-0)
  - (pg# 2525-2649E ) Individuals, miscellaneous, undated (Box 25, Folder 14-0)
  - (pg# 2650-2774E ) Individuals, miscellaneous, undated (Box 25, Folder 14-0)
  - (pg# 2775-2874A ) Individuals, miscellaneous, undated (Box 25, Folder 14-0)
  - (pg# 2875-2949 ) Individuals, miscellaneous, undated (Box 25, Folder 14-0)
  - (pg# 2950-3059 ) Individuals, miscellaneous, undated (Box 25, Folder 14-0)
  - (pg# 3060-3124 ) Individuals, miscellaneous, 1952-1953 (Box 26, Folder 14-0)
  - (pg# 3165-3263 ) Individuals, miscellaneous, 1953 (Box 26, Folder 14-0)
  - (pg# 3264-3380 ) Individuals, miscellaneous, 1953 (Box 26, Folder 14-0)
  - (pg# 3381-3512 ) Individuals, miscellaneous, 1953 (Box 26, Folder 14-0)
  - (pg# 3513-3604 ) Individuals, miscellaneous, 1953 (Box 26, Folder 14-0)
  - (pg# 3605-3729 ) Individuals, miscellaneous, 1953 (Box 26, Folder 14-0)
- Series 14.1: Individuals Named.
  - *Browder, Earl, 1938-1954 (Box 26, Folder 14-1-59)
  - *Gailmor, William S., 1948 (Box 26, Folder 14-2)
  - *Struik, Dirk, 1949 (Box 26, Folder 14-3)
  - Reich, Harry, undated (Box 26, Folder 14-4)
  - Steuben, John, 1950 (Box 26, Folder 14-5)
  - Rubin, Jay, undated (Box 26, Folder 14-6)
  - Schappes, Morris U., undated (Box 26, Folder 14-7)
  - *Epstein, Julius Victor Stefan, 1946 (Box 26, Folder 14-8)
  - *Jaffe, Philip, 1946-1950 (Box 26, Folder 14-9)
  - Shapiro, Nathan B., 1946-1949 (Box 26, Folder 14-10)
  - Ickes, Harold L., 1939 (Box 26, Folder 14-11)
  - Foster, William Z., 1940-1951 (Box 26, Folder 14-12)
  - *Robeson, Paul, 1938-1951 (Box 26, Folder 14-13)
  - *Quill, Michael, 1941-1949 (Box 26, Folder 14-14)
  - Derounian, Avidis (aka George Pagnanelli, John Roy Carlson), 1946-1947 (Box 26, Folder 14-15)
  - *Marcantonio, Vito, 1939-1951 (Box 26, Folder 14-16)
  - Velson, Irving (aka Israel Shavelson, Charles Wilson), 1946 (Box 26, Folder 14-17)
  - Loman, Charles, 1946 (Box 26, Folder 14-18)
  - Stuart, Helen, 1946 (Box 26, Folder 14-19)
  - *Rooney, George H., 1946 (Box 26, Folder 14-20)
  - Marion, George, 1946 (Box 26, Folder 14-21)
  - *Collins, Charles A., 1946 (Box 26, Folder 14-22)
  - *Eisler, Gerhard, 1946-1949 (Box 26, Folder 14-23)
  - Wallace, Henry A., 1948-1950 (Box 26, Folder 14-24)
  - Pepper, Claude, 1942-1950 (Box 26, Folder 14-25)
  - *Draper, Muriel, 1948-1952 (Box 26, Folder 14-26)
  - Yergan, Max, 1947 (Box 26, Folder 14-27)
  - Rosenberg, Milton, 1947 (Box 26, Folder 14-28)
  - *Wolchok, Samuel, 1948 (Box 26, Folder 14-29)
  - Krichwey, Frieda, 1951 (Box 26, Folder 14-30)
  - Smith, Jessica, 1948 (Box 26, Folder 14-31)
  - Terlin, Rose, 1948-1949 (Box 27, Folder 14-32)
  - Lewis, Alfred G. Baker, 1947-1955 (Box 27, Folder 14-33)
  - *Schuman, Frederick L., 1946-1952 (Box 27, Folder 14-34)
  - Connelly, Philip M., 1947 (Box 27, Folder 14-35)
  - *Durkin, James H., 1947-1951 (Box 27, Folder 14-36)
  - Corwin, Norman, 1941-1950 (Box 27, Folder 14-37)
  - *Berney, Leon W., 1947-1950 (Box 27, Folder 14-38)
  - Sherwood, Carlton Montgomery, 1947 (Box 27, Folder 14-39)
  - Roger, Sidney, 1947-1948 (Box 27, Folder 14-40)
  - Condon, Dr. Edward U., 1947-1949 (Box 27, Folder 14-41)
  - *Davis, Benjamin J., 1947-1949 (Box 27, Folder 14-42)
  - Isaacson, Leo, 1948 (Box 27, Folder 14-43)
  - Dewey, Thomas E., 1948-1949 (Box 27, Folder 14-44)
  - Stassen, Harold E., 1948 (Box 27, Folder 14-45)
  - Smith, Ferdinand C., 1948-1950 (Box 27, Folder 14-46)
  - Crum, Bartley C., 1948 (Box 27, Folder 14-47)
  - *Lampell, Millard, 1948-1951 (Box 27, Folder 14-48)
  - Robinson, Edward (Frenchy), 1947 (Box 27, Folder 14-49)
  - Shumlin, Herman, undated (Box 27, Folder 14-49A)
  - *March, Frederic, Mr. and Mrs., 1948 (Box 27, Folder 14-50)
  - *March, Frederic, Mr. and Mrs., 1951? (Box 27, Folder 14-50v2)
  - Rautenstraugh, Walter, 1946 (Box 27, Folder 14-51)
  - Gropper, William, 1949? (Box 27, Folder 14-52)
  - *Hughes, Langston, 1931-1952 (Box 27, Folder 14-53)
  - Buckmaster, Henrietta, 1942-1949 (Box 27, Folder 14-54)
  - McManus, John Thomas, 1942-1947 (Box 27, Folder 14-55)
  - *Sergio, Lisa, 1943-1949 (Box 27, Folder 14-56)
  - *Shipler, Rev. Guy Emery (see also #12-101), 1947-1949 (Box 27, Folder 14-57)
  - Sifton, Paul, 1948 (Box 27, Folder 14-58)
  - Banks, Murray, 1948 (Box 27, Folder 14-59)
  - Cotton, Thomas L., 1948 (Box 27, Folder 14-60)
  - O'Dwyer, Paul, 1948-1949 (Box 27, Folder 14-61)
  - *Gaeth, Arthur, 1948-1949 (Box 27, Folder 14-62)
  - *Addes, George F., 1947 (Box 27, Folder 14-63)
  - Oxnam, Bishop G. Bromley, 1948-1953 (Box 27, Folder 14-64)
  - Kelly, Gener, 1946-1947 (Box 27, Folder 14-65)
  - Ward, Rev. Harry F., 1947-1949 (Box 27, Folder 14-66)
  - Mills, Saul, 1947-1948 (Box 27, Folder 14-67)
  - Oakes Grant, 1948 (Box 27, Folder 14-68)
  - Forge, Maurice (Michael), 1948 (Box 27, Folder 14-69)
  - McMahon, Douglas, 1947 (Box 27, Folder 14-70)
  - Richter, Irving, 1948 (Box 27, Folder 14-71)
  - Melchor, Frederic Gershon, 1948 (Box 27, Folder 14-72)
  - Coughlan, John, 1948 (Box 27, Folder 14-73)
  - Saposs, David Joseph, 1948 (Box 27, Folder 14-74)
  - Marshall, George, 1937-1949 (Box 27, Folder 14-75)
  - McDonough, Bernard J., 1948 (Box 27, Folder 14-76)
  - Pressman, Lee, [1930]-1948 (Box 27, Folder 14-77)
  - Young, Sidney, 1948 (Box 27, Folder 14-78)
  - Lubow, Paul, 1948 (Box 27, Folder 14-79)
  - Altman, Jack, 1948 (Box 27, Folder 14-80)
  - Smith, Willam, 1948 (Box 27, Folder 14-81)
  - Allport, Gordon, 1948 (Box 27, Folder 14-82)
  - Clark, Glenn, 1948 (Box 27, Folder 14-83)
  - *Faber, Gustav, 1946-1947 (Box 27, Folder 14-84)
  - Bishop, L. Melvin, 1948 (Box 27, Folder 14-85)
  - Mattheissen, F.O., 1948-1949 (Box 27, Folder 14-86)
  - Robinson, Earl, 1949 (Box 27, Folder 14-87)
  - Niemeyer, Oscar, 1948 (Box 27, Folder 14-88)
  - Obermeier, Michael J., 1947-1948 (Box 27, Folder 14-89)
  - Kroll, Leon, 1948 (Box 27, Folder 14-90)
  - Ryan, John F., 1947 (Box 27, Folder 14-91)
  - Davis, Leon J., 1948 (Box 27, Folder 14-92)
  - Barnes, Harry Elmer, 1947 (Box 27, Folder 14-93)
  - *Draper, Paul, 1949 (Box 27, Folder 14-94)
  - Thomas, Norman, 1948-1953 (Box 27, Folder 14-95)
  - Richardson, Dr. Henry B., 1952 (Box 27, Folder 14-96)
  - Metz, Julius, 1948 (Box 27, Folder 14-97)
  - Miley, Paul E., 1949 (Box 27, Folder 14-98)
  - *Johnson, Manning, 1941 (Box 27, Folder 14-99)
  - Dennis, Eugene, 1946-1950 (Box 27, Folder 14-100)
  - Gates, John, 1948-1949 (Box 27, Folder 14-101)
  - Stachel, Jacob A. (Jack), 1948 (Box 27, Folder 14-102)
  - Williamson, John, 1948-1949 (Box 27, Folder 14-103)
  - Winston, Henry, 1948-1949 (Box 27, Folder 14-104)
  - Dana, Henry Wadsworth Longfellow, 1947? (Box 27, Folder 14-105)
  - Bradley, Prof Lyman R., 1948 (Box 27, Folder 14-106)
  - +Beall, Jack, 1948 (Box 27, Folder 14-107)
  - Garfield, John, 1947-1950 (Box 27, Folder 14-108)
  - *Rogge, O. John, 1948-1949 (Box 27, Folder 14-109)
  - *Adamic, Louis, 1946-1948 (Box 27, Folder 14-110)
  - Berne, Lewis Alan, 1947-1949 (Box 27, Folder 141-111)
  - Black, Algernon D., undated (Box 27, Folder 14-112)
  - Goldsmith, Leonard (Len), 1948 (Box 27, Folder 14-113)
  - Simmons, Ernest J., 1950 (Box 27, Folder 14-114)
  - Gaer, Joseph, 1948 (Box 27, Folder 14-115)
  - Belfrage, Cedric, 1948-1953 (Box 27, Folder 14-116)
  - Elliot, Dr. & Mrs. Harrison S., undated (Box 27, Folder 14-117)
  - Smith, Hilda Worthington, undated (Box 27, Folder 14-118)
  - Riskin, Benjamin H., 1948 (Box 27, Folder 14-119)